I'm sure it's quite the traumatic experience
being eaten alive by your own sister.
Then again,
when a man uncovers his deepest desires,
all of his weaknesses are laid bare.
You gave Nary a thought
to the depraved nature of
bringing someone back to
the world of the living.
Everyone desperately wants to believe that
their loved ones are
still alive somewhere.
More than anything else,
your hope is that by some miracle
they'll suddenly pop in tomorrow and say,
good morning.
Oh, before I forget, I believe you
said something about a third wish.
But if I'm not mistaken,
you've already made said wish.
You mean...
You wish for Avdol to come back to life!
Hail to you!
No, he's...
And now,
I'm a star-dust It's
called 100 years ago
The young men are facing The time
This is time for me!
After all it's me!
After all why?
My fingers, they've crumpled to pieces.
On your feet, Polnareff!
I blame you for all of this because
of your idiotic, bumbling eye.
Polnareff, because of
you I ended up like this!
Avdol, you're right.
The person to blame for this is me!
Mark my words, you'll pay for this,
Polnareff, and you'll do it with your flesh!
I'll get better if I eat, right?
Well, am I right?
Oh, big brother!
What's the matter, brother?
Stay away!
Stay away from me!
Both of you, please go
back to your graves!
But why?
You're the one who brought
us back, aren't you?
The time has come for
you to enter your grave!
I'm so panicked that I
forgot to summon chariots!
How could I have been so caught up in my
wish that I neglected to use my stand?
Leave me alone!
Get away from me!
Please, just stay away!
What the? Please?
Oh, no, no, no.
You don't have any wishes left, remember?
I've already granted your three wishes.
And I'm sorry to say,
you don't get any more.
Stop it! Get off!
Hail to you!
Go ahead, writhe and scream to
your pathetic heart's content.
Since you're in the middle of nowhere,
your friends by the shore won't hear you.
No one can save you now!
It's no use.
This is the end.
I'm going to die.
I'm finished.
Sherry... Avdol...
I suppose you're giving
me what I deserved.
It's only fitting.
It's like you said.
You died because of my actions.
And so, I've accepted my fate.
What?
My vision must be going.
I'm seeing double.
It looks like there are two Avdals.
Huh?
Of course there's not another one.
If I'm starting to see things,
guess it means the end is near.
The blood loss is taking its toll.
I'm hallucinating.
All right.
This is it.
I'll have to tap out early.
Goodbye, Mr. Joestar.
Kakyoin.
Jotaro.
I pray for your victory.
As for you, Avdol.
I'll atone in the next world.
What? Impossible!
I was right.
I just knew I saw another Avdol.
My eyes weren't playing tricks.
Besides the dirt and dust version
cameo made, there's another Avdol.
Magicians run!
But how?
He's supposed to be dead.
It's impossible.
He was stabbed by the
hangman's centerfold.
How the hell is he alive?
Are you really Mohammed Avdol?
Yes, you have better believe I am.
Is it?
Really, you?
Is it the real you, I mean?
Polnareff, you haven't
changed in the slightest.
You still lose all common
sense when it comes to your
sister and never stop to
think of the consequences.
I simply refuse to accept this.
Muhammad Avdol is dead!
I was told whole horse put a
bullet between your eyes after
hangman sunk his blade into your
back and you died on the spot.
You're correct about me being
shot right in the forehead.
That said because I was stabbed
in the back for a moment
my face was looking up and
the bullet only grazed me I.
Suppose this is what one would
call a blessing in disguise.
Holehorse didn't realize it.
But his bullet never made
contact with my brain,
so he didn't inflict a mortal wound.
He was only able to scratch
my skin and bruise my skull.
Although I did completely
lose consciousness.
So you call yourself Cameo
of the Judgment card.
Hell is near.
So prepare.
For hell to you!
I know it was only the third
wish, but still, it's really him.
It came true.
Muhammad Avdol is indeed alive and well.
I would call this bad news.
That being the case,
shouldn't you scurry away
to inform Dio and your
fellow stand-user
compatriots about my return?
Well, shouldn't you, Cameo?
That's right!
I have to tell them!
I have to let Mr.
Joestar, Kakyoin, and
Jotaro know! Avdol's back!
This is very surprising news to be sure,
but the way I see it,
I can spin it this way!
Not only did Judgment's cameo
slay the idiot Balnareff?
but also succeeded in eliminating Avdol?
who was actually alive!
Oh, I can't wait to tell
them the splendid news!
Maticians, run!
Whoa there!
Avdol!
This stand, it's four more
powerful than I expected.
Be careful, it's not just his power!
This guy's got incredible speed too.
Come now, Avdol, is that the
extent of your abilities?
If so, then sharing my good news
will be even easier than expected.
May Fortune
Be with you both?
What now?
Hail to you!
My brother?
No, stop this charade.
You're not the real Sherry.
My Sherry is gone. Dead.
You're nothing but a hunk of dirt!
But, brother…
Polnareff, apologies.
I would like to take back what
I said about you not changing.
No, you were right about me all along.
I'm the one who should apologize.
This battle has already been decided!
Tell you what!
After all, before you head off
for that magic lamp in the sky?
I'd like to hear your three wishes.
I'll grant them before I
put you to rest for good
Go ahead.
You may as well give it a shot.
As I said, you get three wishes Kel salut.
He's making fools of us.
Just ignore him, Avdol.
You don't have to make any wishes
Avdol, are you listening to me?
No good
I want four wishes. Huh?
What?
My wishes.
Can't you hear?
I'm asking you to grant my wishes.
Only I want four instead of three.
Avdol, you can't be serious.
Are you denying my wish?
Cameo, you're the one who
offered to grant them.
I'm going to make sure
you keep your promise.
You still insist upon this
futile contest of power?
Your kicks are nothing!
What?
That's the way! Super!
You should probably know that my first
wish was to make you cry out in agony.
And it came true.
This is madness.
How can you be so much
stronger than before?
The wound left behind
after I was stabbed by
the Hanged Man hasn't
completely healed yet.
Because I was so focused on
guarding my wound from an assault,
I had to hold myself back a little. What?
It was only three days ago that I
was finally able to stand again.
But since I took a plane here from
India, the trip was very easy.
That's Avdol.
Still the best.
And now, for my second wish!
I wish for you to scream
out in utter terror.
And while you're at it,
grant my third wish.
Cry and regret.
Fat bastard!
He's running away!
Wait, damn it!
Get back here!
Shh!
Polnareff, quiet.
With that kind of power
and speed given the
rule of stands the user
must be hiding somewhere
nearby supplying his
stand with
energy
is he
here yes he should be
hiding out very close to us?
Oh, hey, could that be...
Shhh...
Has this user really resorted
to hiding underground?
Damn coward, how dare you use my
sister like some pawn in a game!
For what you've done, I
think I'll show you hell!
Hell to you!
Corner!
I can think of a few things
to drop down this tube.
Like dirt and sand.
A spider,
ants too?
and a match.
Bastard, I hope you're ready because
your suffering has barely begun.
Hey, Polnareff,
I do believe it's time
for me to drain the snake.
How about it, my friend?
Shall we engage in the timeless
ritual of male bonding? Hmm.
Somehow I made it out of that mess alive.
Huh?
Come on, Boulder F, let me hear you laugh.
I want to hear the hardiest
laugh that you can muster.
Avdol, I might be wrong about this, but it
seems like you're the one who's changed.
Before the incident,
you would have never thought of
doing something quite so perverse.
This...
this isn't a result of you
being shot in the head, is it?
That's it! Aim that thing!
Right!
Huh?
What the...?
Please, I beg you, forgive me!
Last but not least, my fourth wish
is to not grant you a single
one of your pitiful wishes.
My Magician's Red forgives no one,
especially not you.
Oh!
Badumps!
Hey!
You guys will never believe it!
Guess who I ran into while out and about?
Polnareff, we were worried about you.
Where did those injuries come from?
Some kind of enemy.
My wounds are nothing compared to my news!
Now listen up and don't
be too shocked, Jotaro!
And you're gonna have to promise you
won't throw your back out and surprise,
Kakyoin!
Who do you think I met out there, Mr.
Joestar?
Now prepare to be blown away!
Tum-ta-da-da!
Here he is!
That sly bastard Avdol is
still alive, isn't that great?
Well, we should probably get going.
Here, allow me to help
you carry your luggage.
Avdol, how you been doing?
It's been a while.
How goes it?
So, Avdol, is the wound on
your back healing up all right?
It's fine, though my joints do
get a little stiff sometimes.
Hey!
Has it really been two weeks
since we last saw each other?
Hey!
We're lucky to all be alive.
Jotaro, you're still wearing your uniform?
Don't you ever get hot?
Hey, just hold on a second, guys.
Didn't you hear me?
I told you to hold on
a second, you assholes.
What's the deal with those
laissez-faire attitudes?
A man we thought was dead
just waltzed onto the beach.
How the hell can you just brush it
off and act like nothing has changed?
Oh, yeah, I'm sorry about that, Polnareff.
When I told you I'd taken it upon myself
to bury Avdol in India, I may have lied.
What the hell?! Mr.
Joestar and Jotaro were the
ones who tended to the wounds
on my head back in India after
I was shot by Hull Horse.
You assholes have known Avdol was
alive the entire time and never
once stood across any of your
deceitful minds to let me know!
I'm most surprised at you, Kakyoin!
I only found out the day
after it all happened,
But it was imperative to
not let the enemy know,
and since you have such a big mouth,
I suggested... Pardon.
What I meant to say was, since it's
not easy for you to lie on command,
I suggested we keep it a secret from you.
If you'd let the secret slip, Avdol wouldn't
have been able to recuperate in peace.
We were planning to let you know the
very moment we knew that he was safe.
But we didn't think
you'd run into him first.
Oh, yeah!
Avdol, we found your dad
living in a hut on this island!
Come on, let's let him know you're here!
Oh, that was just me in disguise.
Say what?
Then you were in on it
from the very start?
Everything that happened
was a ruse you created?
Don't talk to me!
No one ever comes to visit when
they have good news to report!
Just shut up!
Don't go there.
Avdol's death wasn't your fault.
You didn't have to go that far!
How dare you leave me out of the loop!
I think that's the cruelest
thing you've ever done to me!
Now, now, chin up.
There's no reason for you to cry.
I'm sorry, Polnareff.
I truly didn't think you'd be this hurt.
I apologize as well,
but I had a very good reason for
coming to this island in disguise.
Yeah, what is it?
It was partially so the
enemy wouldn't find out.
But I also had Abdal do some shopping
for me while he was laying low.
What kind of shopping?
Since it was a very
conspicuous acquisition,
I disguised myself as a
wealthy Arab gentleman.
All right, everyone.
Let's climb aboard and head out.
Come on, Polnareff.
For the love of everything
that's sacred, cheer up already.
Huh?
It's almost here.
Look!
I don't understand what's almost here.
I don't see anything!
What?
Whoa!
A submarine!
That's right.
From here on out,
we're riding to egypt in this you you've
got to be kidding how did you afford this?
all your paintings on the tomb they
do the sand dance don't you know?
if they move too quick they're
falling down like a domino
on the buzzer men by the
nile they got the money on a
bed called crocodiles they
snap their teeth on your
cigarette foreign types with
a hookah walk
like
an egyptian
the blonde waitresses take
their trays spin around and they
cross the floor they've got
the moves you drop your drink
then they bring you more all
the school kids so sick of books
they like the punk and the
metal band when the buzzer rings
they're walking like an egyptian all
the kids in the marketplace say wayo,
wayo, wayo, wayo, wayo
walk like an egyptian
the sparkly design is
much more to my liking?
A submarine, huh?
Perhaps a refreshing
white would be better?
Hurry and make the coffee!
Which one should I pick?
Kakuwi, why'd you grab
six cups? Yes, hello?
Oh, Joseph, darling, it's you!